groupee.com 2006-06-16

# Groupee: Privacy Statement

**Groupee Respects Your Privacy**

Groupee respects your privacy. That's why we have created this Privacy Statement to explain how and why we collect certain information online, and how we use that information. This statement also explains how you can prevent collection of certain information about yourself, if you choose. Please take a few moments to read our Privacy Statement. This statement applies to both information we collect from visitors to the Groupee.com Web site (and other Groupee websites, such as UBBCentral.com), as well as information we collect or have access to when we host communities for other websites. 

**Right to Change Policy**

As Groupee is constantly innovating and enhancing the products and services it provides to its users, this Privacy Statement will also continue to change to match the products and services we make available. As such, we reserve the right to change this statement to match the products and services we provide. If we make any material change to this statement, we will change the date at the top of this statement to reflect the effective date of the change. When you visit our site or use our products and services, we encourage you to check the date of this Privacy Statement to ensure you are aware of any updates. However, regardless of how this Privacy Statement may change or evolve over time, Groupee will not collect or maintain your private and personally identifiable information without your consent. Further, if you consent to give us your personal information, we will keep it confidential and will not sell, license or disclose your personal information to any third party without your consent, unless we are compelled to do so under the law or to comply with a court order. Note that if you use our login on a participating site (a site using the Groupee Network login), that site will have access to the email address that you have registered, but will not have access to your password. 

**Contact for Privacy Inquiries**

If you have any questions about this Privacy Statement or other questions about privacy on the Groupee site, please contact: 

**Via Mail:**  
Groupee, Inc.  
Privacy Contact: Groupee Privacy Administrator   
2401 4th Avenue, Suite 500  
Seattle, WA 98121 USA

**Online:**  

**Types of Information We Collect**

Generally, you are free to browse the Groupee.com site without submitting any personal information. We do not collect any of your personal information (such as a name, address or email address) when you visit the Groupee site, unless you license and/or download one of our products, register or have registered to use one of our products or services, complete one of our evaluations, or otherwise agree to submit to us such information. As part of such processes, you have the opportunity to decline further promotional materials or other notifications from us regarding special offers and information from Groupee. Types of information collected on specific services on the Groupee.com site are described in more detail below. 

**Registration on Our Site**

Groupee requires users who want to participate in the Groupee Support Community to register. In order to register, you must provide us with a verifiable email address and password. This allows us to protect our community from abusive postings and provides a verifiable point of contact should legal questions arise. At any time, you have the ability to keep your email address hidden from other users by selecting that option within your user profile. 

When you register, you have the option of providing some additional information such as occupation, interests, and homepage URL. This optional information is made available to other community users to foster a sense of community. If you have any concerns about providing this information, simply leave the fields blank and your registration will still be processed. 

**IF YOU ARE UNDER 13 YEARS OF AGE you are not allowed to participate in the Groupee Support Community.**

**Online Purchases**

If you choose a service or transaction that requires payment, such as signing up for a community plan or licensing UBB.threads or UBB.classic, we will request personal information necessary for billing and/or shipping, such as: name, address, telephone number, and credit card information. We keep this information secure and use it only for billing purposes. 

**Community Services**

When you use our Groupee Community services through a third party Web site, the collection, storage, maintenance and use of the information you submit on the third party Web site is generally governed by the privacy policy of the third party, even though all such information is stored on Groupee's servers. Groupee is contractually prohibited from accessing or using any of the private, personally identifiable information that you submit to the third party as part of your registration and use of that product on the third party site. An exception to this is your login information, if the third party site is using our Groupee Network login; in that case, we are collecting your login email address and password. You should refer to the privacy policy of the third party if you have any questions regarding the third party's collection, storage, maintenance and use of your information. As part of Groupee's provision of the Groupee Community Service to third party Web sites, Groupee does use a cookie to collect non-personally identifiable information about your access and use of Groupee Community Services on third party Web sites. These cookies do not collect, store or maintain your private, personally identifiable information and Groupee does not and will not match such cookie information with any private, personally identifying information you submit on such site. You are not required to accept this cookie to use Groupee Community Services on third party sites (though by rejecting it, your overall experience on the third party community may be diminished). You may choose to refuse our cookie, or you may delete or turn off our cookie from your hard drive at any time. Groupee uses the non-personally identifiable information collected about your access and use of our services through the third party site in accordance with our general policy regarding cookies. See below for information on collection and use of cookie information. 

**Newsletter Subscription**

Groupee offers an option to subscribe to a periodic newsletter regarding our company's activities, promotions, product announcements and news items. The only piece of information required is the user's email address, which is only used to distribute the requested newsletter. You can "unsubscribe" to the newsletter at any time by following the instructions at the bottom of the newsletter. 

**Cookies**

Groupee uses browser cookies to facilitate your experience with our products and services. These cookies are small sections of code that our server sends to your browser which it can then store on your hard drive. If you choose to accept these cookies, they enable us to recognize that your browser has previously visited and used our site, products or services and, based on your browser's previous visits, assist us with tailoring the information and content, banners and promotions you view. These cookies also enable us to recognize when you access and use Groupee's OpenTopic product on third party Web sites. An example of the customization allowed by the use of such cookies is to retain your username and password as part of the Support Forums on our site so you don't have to re-enter them each time you visit. These cookies do not collect, store or maintain your private, personally identifiable information. You do not have to accept these cookies to visit or use the Groupee site or our products and services, and you can choose to refuse our cookie, delete our cookie from your hard drive or turn off the Groupee cookie at any time by updating your user profile preferences. 

**Purchasing and/or Credit Card Information**

Groupee strives to maintain strict security for your private information. Our online ordering pages are processed over a Secure Socket Layer (SSL), providing a secure means of ordering our products. All credit card information collected by Groupee is encrypted in our databases to provide further security. 

**Technical Support**

Any personal information you provide to us in the course of obtaining technical support, or asking other questions about Groupee will be used only for the purposes for which it was submitted. We may store the information, but we will not use it for any other purposes or intentionally distribute it to any third parties. 

**Use and Disclosure of Your Information**

Groupee uses the personal information it collects from forms you fill out on our site or in our product and service registrations to: 

  1. Allow users to access and use our products and services; 
  2. Supply users with installation instructions, download, access or use information, and technical support information; 
  3. Provide users of products and service on our site with information about special offers and promotions; and 
  4. Improve our products and services by using statistical analysis and evaluation of user data. 

We do not and will not disclose your private, personally identifiable information to any third party for any purpose without your prior consent. However, Groupee reserves the right to disclose your personal information if required to do so by law, or in the good faith belief that such action is reasonably necessary to comply with legal process, respond to claims, or to protect the rights, property or safety of our company, its employees, customers, or the public. 

All reasonable care is taken by our staff in handling your personal information to ensure its security both offline and online. It is our policy to destroy server access and any personal information provided during the technical support process upon completion of the technical support incident. 

**Changing or Updating Personal Information**

If you would like to update or change your user profile on our Support Community, you may do so online at any time. 

To unsubscribe to our Groupee newsletter, please follow the specific unsubscribe instructions at the bottom of the newsletter. 

To update the information on your registered UBB.classic or UBB.threads license, visit the [UBB Member Area](http://infopop.com/members/members.php). 

To update your Groupee Community billing information, log into your [Groupee Community Customer Account](https://admin.groupee.com/customer.php). 

If you have questions regarding your information, you can contact our Privacy Administrator at the address listed above. 

**Postings on Online Communities**

It is important for you to remain aware that when you provide personal information (e.g., last name, address, phone number) in a posting on any online community, that information may be available to any other person or user having access and use of that community, and may be used by someone in a manner unintended by you. For that reason, we discourage you from offering any personally identifying information within a posting to any community. 

Last Updated June 16, 2005
